(The Destination Is Happiness)
Nice to see you all.
Look how much our studio changed.
- Doesn't it look nice? - It looks great.
- What do you think? - It looks very colorful.
- It's... - We still have Wilson teddy bears.
But he's got some friends by his side.
- Right. - Gosh.
It feels like it's the Children's Day.
Now that it's May,
- Right. - we have...
building blocks.
I really like toys like building blocks.
This especially caught my eye.
If you look on the right, you'll see it.
- Okay. - That's really popular now.
- What's popular? - It's trending.
- Pikachu. - Pikachu?
It's exclusively available here within the Asian market.
Really?
- Oh, that guy? - Yes.
I should buy one for my dad right away.
- This is great for elders. - They'll love it. Seriously.
- For your dad? - What?
- Wouldn't cash be better? - You'll give it to your dad?
Elders love assembling toys like this.
Actually, we're not featuring these building blocks...
- for the Children's Day. - Okay.
- These toys are meant for adults. - That's... Yes.
- Right. - I see.
- I tried it when I turned 30. - Yes.
I could only focus on building the toys one at a time,
stress-free and without thinking about anything.
It was such a joy.
- It's perfect for that. - I see.
- It is. - Yes.
It's great not only for that, but also for interior design.
- It's great. - It is.
- There are different figures too. - By the way,
- there's one for Wilson. - Yes.
Is that version also available in the market?
Oh, that? It was built exclusively...
for our show.
It's the rarest limited edition.
- Wilson looks so cute as a toy. - He does.
- He looks so cute. - He does look cute.
On our show, she was portrayed as a little kid...
who would love to play with these building blocks.
- It's been a while, Shin Young. - Yes. My gosh.
Nice to see you all.
I bet you got an incredible response...
- after your episode aired. - Right.
- The response was insane. - It was.
So...
(Her clips got a fiery response just like the hot glass noodles.)
(- Kim Shin Young has returned. - It feels great to watch her eat.)
(Watching her brings me peace, comfort, and joy.)
After I got the nickname, Charlie and the Glass Noodle Factory,
glass noodles were sold out.
- You're as influential as G-DRAGON. - Of course.
You can call me FOOD-DRAGON.
(I'm FOOD-DRAGON.)
FOOD-DRAGON.
- I wanted to meet with you. - Okay.
- Many people reached out about you. - What did they say?
- In the world of bulking up, - Yes.
- you're like our leader. - "In the world of bulking up?"
- So... - "Bulking up?"
- of everything you said, - Yes.
so many of those comments resonated with me.
- Like what? - Like what?
"When I wake up, my appetite is on fire."
(My appetite is on fire in the morning.)
- Right. - Not a lot of people have...
- a big appetite in the morning. - Right.
Only 2 out of 10 people would be hungry, and that's us.
I'm hungry the moment I wake up.
I had spicy stir-fried pork for breakfast.
(Loving it)
- I had kimchi fried rice. - This is...
- This is like a family reunion. - I had breakfast too.
- How many times will they clap? - We are...
(Let's do it one more time.)
We're not watching their videos today, by the way.
- Right. No. - My gosh. We should calm down.
Okay.
In today's clips, you'll see Na Ra, Ji Hyeon,
- and me. That's right. - My gosh.
I'll show you why I gathered around these kind-hearted friends.
Let's watch it now.
(The Fun Start)
- How are you feeling? - Me? I feel great.
- How are you feeling? - What?
- I feel great too. - You do?
- The 2 of them met up. - They met up 1st.
- This place is nice. - I see.
(Glancing)
- I'm glad the weather is nice. - Yes.
I thought it might be cold.
- Right. We're in Gangwon Province. - Yes.
Dowoon, should we drop the honorifics now?
- Should we? Right. - We're the same age.
(Should we?)
You guys didn't drop the honorifics at first.
We were the same age, but we kept speaking with honorifics.
Let's speak casually now.
- Okay. - Yes.
Let's speak casually.
(Fidgeting)
- We're the same age. - Right.
It was really awkward.
The vibe between you two reminds me of "I Am Solo."
- Right. - It does.
You guys are just missing suitcases.
- That's it. - Right here.
- But it must be a red suitcase. - Right.
(They arrive at the gazebo while feeling awkward.)
This is nice.
It's nice here.
(They sit down in front of a beautiful view.)
(Scratching)
That bird over there looks cool in that pose.
- Right. - Yes.
(Chuckling)
Those jerks!
- I was super nice to them. - Dowoon...
(I was super nice to them.)
- Did they ditch you? - They ditched me!
- They ditched you. - How did this happen?
- They came to a stress-free side. - Wait.
- Right. - Seriously. Come on.
I took them to a fishing spot and a dry sauna.
I bought them all the tasty food.
Are you all right?
(Something's wrong.)
(They shared memories as heroes.)
(They also shared each other's temperature.)
(The Kiwoon Duo were happy together.)
Imagine how difficult it must've been for them.
That's why they joined me.
I was good to Ji Hyeon.
My gosh.
But you can't invite both of us at once.
(But you can't invite both of us at once.)
Yes, I can!
- You invited us separately. - Hey.
- Right. - A handshake.
You can't take care of two people at once.
Now that you're with Hyun Moo, you're so harsh.
- He learned from the best. - Leaders...
- must be able to embrace all. - Seriously.
What's the point of inviting people...
- separately? - Ji Hyeon has gotten feisty.
- Did you embrace all three? - I can embrace them all.
I can even embrace four people at once.
You little...
(You know that I'm joking, right?)
You must not get a lot of chances to enjoy the view like this.
- Right. Especially not lately. - Right.
I'm always in the car.
It's been a while since I last saw the ocean too.
(Smiling brightly)
Who's that? My gosh. He came out of nowhere.
Hey.
He's smiling there like a fool from the neighborhood.
- Where did you come from? - I...
- He's got nice legs. - Yes.
Why did he dress like that?
- It's like a scene in a drama. - Why do I look so weird?
You know what gave me the goosebumps?
- He only wore underpants that day. - No.
Did you leave Seoul, dressed like that?
Yes.
This will be a legendary entrance scene.
- Let me explain. - You told him...
to dress appropriately since you would go for a run.
I did make that clear.
The Fun Run is all about the gear.
(The Fun Run is all about the gear.)
When will he get here?
(Approaching stealthily)
It's different.
(Clueless of his approach, they keep gazing afar.)
When will he get here?
What? My gosh.
Hello.
- "I am..." - He looks like a fool.
- What? - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
- My name is Bae Na Ra. - I know.
- I see. - Of course, I know.
- Have you been well? - Yes.
They all feel awkward.
- You're dressed for a run. - Yes. I...
- I see. - Did you already go for a run?
Well, running is part of my daily life.
- Really? - Yes. Hyun Moo invited me...
for a run today.
So I dressed appropriately for the run.
I see.
- You're all here for a run, right? - Of course.
- Are you all dressed for it? - Yes.
(Fully ready)
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
As a follower...
- of the Fun Run, - That's right.
I was told he was going to form the first batch for the Fun Run.
That's why I'm here.
Well, Hyun Moo...
invited me to join his Fun Run.
(Inhaling sharply)
Why did he invite me?
You just went there without knowing why you were invited.
I was curious...
what this Fun Run was all about.
I'll be honest. I got the chills.
- You invited three obedient people. - Right.
Right.
I only invited people who would never say no to me.
- You got obedient, easygoing ones. - Right.
- I only invited meek ones. - Right.
Na Ra also said that I was his favorite.
(He had been Kian84's fan for a very long time.)
Thank you.
(Na Ra bravely revealed that on the show.)
- You're too much for him too. - Right.
- I like Kian84. - He's so gentle.
- I lost them all. - You lost them to him.
He took my people and my hobby.
(But you still have me.)
I keep feeling like... How should I put it?
I'm star-struck.
- No, we feel the same way. - Us too.
(A bright smile)
(Gosh, it's too bright for my eyes.)
Look at his smile.
(Flashing his smile)
- You have a beautiful smile. - By the way...
He has such a beautiful smile. And he also has dimples.
- He had this positive energy. - Thank you.
The moment I met him,
I got the feeling that he'd be a devoted church-goer.
When we first said hello to each other,
I could feel that he was a kind-hearted man.
- I could feel their kindness. - It was nice.
What draws you to running?
The sense of achievement definitely plays a big role.
- It's similar to hiking. - So...
- Right. - Ji Hyeon and I aren't...
completely sold on running.
- Really? - We don't know much about running.
Maybe, I run twice a year or something.
- We welcome... - I see.
- guys like him. - That's why.
- I'll help you guys. - Thank you.
- You know, people do this too. - Yes.
Some people "hijack" mountains.
- Hijacking is like... - That's...
Hijacking is seizing vehicles.
- Dowoon isn't good at English. - Really?
- He is. - Is that so?
- Do you mean trail running? - I see.
- Have you tried that? - Yes, I have.
- My gosh. - I can tackle small mountains.
I can run up about 5km.
It's really fun.
- By the way... - Did Hyun Moo tell you...
when he would be here? Did he tell you that?
He only told me to show up.
(Quiet)
I think he's late.
He's just late.
He won't say he can't make it, right?
(Feeling guilty)
- But that won't be so bad. - I agree. It'll still be fun.
- We can... - What if they run without him?
I really want to run. It's driving me crazy.
This is crazy.
(A crazy urge to run)
This feels great.
(Guys, give me a bit more time.)
(Sucking)
Oh, I hate this!
The air feels so fresh.
(The crew chief of the Fun Run is running to them.)
My gosh, look at these stairs. I should walk up.
Climbing the stairs isn't fun.
Darn it. Why did I ask to meet them here?
Look at him.
(Panting)
There were so many stairs.
Is drinking water a mission or something? This is...
This isn't good. I'm already tired.
(This isn't good. I'm already tired.)
(Huddled up)
That's interesting.
- The next-closest one? - Yes.
You should speak casually to us.
- You should drop the honorifics. - You should drop the honorifics.
- Should I do that? - Yes, please.
Let's do that then. Nice to meet you.
- Great. - Nice to meet you.
Will we need sunglasses later when we start running?
I...
- I can drop the honorifics now. - Yes.
When you're running,
- the wind might blow against you. - I see.
Dust can go into your eyes.
- They didn't know I was there. - So...
I brought my sunglasses.
- I came well-prepared. - My gosh. What?
- I see. - My gosh. What?
- I see. - Gosh.
(They finally spot the crew chief.)
I thought he was going to fall.
- Are you that happy to see me? - Hello.
It looks like you guys are getting along.
I thought you guys might feel awkward with each other.
Gosh, Hyun Moo. Are you wearing makeup?
I've never seen anyone wear makeup when they go for a run.
- That's the Fun Run. - My gosh. I hate it.
You sort of look like a cotton swab. You know?
Your face is white, but your neck is brown.
(White and dark)
I had to put on some makeup since I was running with you guys.
- You didn't? - We didn't.
- Sit down. - Okay.
- The white cast is very noticeable. - It is?
The Fun Run will open up a new horizon in the running scene.
To hold the inauguration ceremony for the first batch...
You're so good at taking all the credit.
(Moomoo's Fun Run took the running scene by storm.)
- It was shaped like a puppy. - Right.
Will it be different today?
It will be different today.
I'm going to form the Fun Run Crew.
(He decided to form a crew.)
I picked guys who wouldn't be stressed...
from running.
I picked Dowoon.
It seems he's only interested in boxing and nothing else.
That's great.
I welcome people who love lounging around at home.
It looks like running will never be a regular hobby for him.
I picked Ji Hyeon.
(Ji Hyeon is a couch potato.)
I chose Na Ra. He showed us a weird style of running...
when he went camping.
(The follower of the Fun Run, Na Ra)
I focused on that.
Your pace is quite fast for the Fun Run.
I picked these three guys for the crew.
(I thought long and hard to pick these three guys.)
The kind-hearted trio.
They have this desire to run.
I'll bring out this desire from them and that's why I invited them.
We'll start small.
(Every history has a beginning.)
I keep seeing this word, "history."
(The Birth of the 1st Fun Run Crew)
As it so happens, I read...
this news article today that some people had finished...
the marathon under two hours.
- Today? - Really?
- Really? - Someone broke that record.
- Really? - Two people did.
It happened at the London Marathon?
Finishing the marathon under two hours...
- had been a goal for mankind. - Right.
So this is the world we live in now. But the Fun Run...
If you can't accomplish that,
- our approach will be better. - It's better to have fun with it.
- It's better to have fun. - Of course.
Do you know why we came here?
Do you know why we're holding our inauguration ceremony here?
- Where's your hometown? - Mokpo.
- It's Jeolla Province, right? - Yes.
- What about you? - Gyeongsang Province.
- Gyeongsang Province, right? - Yes.
- Chungcheong Province, right? - Right.
- I'm from Seoul. - Yes.
Which province is missing?
- Gangwon Province. - Gangwon Province.
We're missing Gangwon Province. That's why we're having it here.
(That's why the ceremony is here.)
- There's a story to the Fun Run. - He's good at making stories.
It's meaningful to have it here this year because 2026 is...
the Year of Visit Gangwon.
That's this year.
- We're visiting it. - Yes, we are. It starts today.
This is the first shot of our national anthem video.
- Until the East Sea - Until the East Sea
(The Fun Run Crew is meeting up at the Chuam Beach.)
To celebrate the foundation of the Fun Run Crew's first batch,
I wanted us to receive new energy from there.
That could help our crew be successful.
I'll show you a lot of beautiful spots today.
- Are you ready for the Fun Run? - Yes.
- Should we start running now? - No.
- I brought some food. - What's that?
- Do you want to eat first? - My gosh.
- You brought us food? - Yes. I heard...
cucumbers were good before running.
Cucumbers are great.
- Yes. - Ji Hyeon is thoughtful like that.
Thank you.
It will be refreshing once you take a bite.
(Humming)
This is so admirable of you.
- How diligent. You woke up early. - Right.
(They get to hydrate thanks to Ji Hyeon.)
I was touched by his thoughtful side.
Hold on.
- I brought this just in case. - Okay.
- I know this is the Fun Run. - Yes.
I wanted us to run with a sense of unity.
- I brought tapes for our knees. - Good.
- Everyone came well-prepared. - We need them.
Watching this clip makes me want to run.
Do you want to join us?
- Do you want to join us? - Not that. I should form my own.
- To pursue the essence of running. - You'll form your own?
- A legit running crew? - Yes.
You should run with MINHO.
- For your legit crew. - That sounds good.
Then he's the only one who can join.
- It's just him. - We wouldn't join his.
If you're not happy with his Fun Run,
I'll let you join my crew.
A legit running crew sounds a bit daunting.
You and I should go and get some food.
I'll just sit in front of the beach.
Right. Same here. Let's eat cucumbers with chogochujang.
Actually, I know three great restaurants by the East Sea.
They became best friends.
(We prefer Fun Eating, not the Fun Run.)
I want to try that. You brought them for us.
- Hey. - Let's do it now.
Gosh. Your legs are so white.
- Let's do it now. - Gosh.
Your legs are so white.
- They're so white. - Look at his legs.
- They're so white. - My goodness.
- My goodness. - Look at his legs.
- Gosh. - They're milky white.
They're as white as milk.
Gosh, you're wearing a lot of them.
Hey, that looks really fancy.
I wanted to match it with yours.
- I see. - Why did I dress like that?
- Right here. - Isn't that too tight, though?
Isn't that too tight, though?
(Tight)
Actually, I prepared a lot for the Fun Run.
I really thought we'd be running a lot.
So you wore underpants.
No, that's a typical outfit in running crews.
- Right? - They treated you like a weirdo...
- because it was the Fun Run. - I became a weirdo.
- By the way... - That's a standard look.
- Right? Thank you. - Yes.
I could easily see his silhouette.
He's treated like a weirdo because it's a weird running crew.
The crew chief applied too much foundation on his face.
The more I watch this, the angrier I'm getting.
Why are you so angry? We didn't even start running.
(I'll bring down the Fun Run.)
I'll put on the tapes with utmost care.
- That's the hairiest part. - He put it on the hairiest part.
- I've done this a lot. - Yes.
Stretch your legs.
- You must have creases here. - What?
- It means it's done properly. - That looks so gross.
Like this.
Did you put on sunscreen on your legs?
No. They're just dry patches.
You just wait until you get old.
You get them on the most unexpected places.
- Come on. Seriously? - Oh, gross. I didn't want to know.
It happens, you know?
No. You look great.
- Thank you. - Sure.
(Na Ra carefully puts tapes on Dowoon's and Ji Hyeon's legs too.)
- Okay. You get it now, right? - Yes.
It feels good.
- It feels good? - It feels tight, right?
Thank you.
(Groaning)
Oh, it's my leg hair. Darn it.
- Will this be okay? - I'm sorry.
- That looks gross. - You have hair on your knees too?
By the way,
becoming a regular member of this crew isn't easy.
Okay. Are there rules?
- I need to test your basic fitness. - Sure.
- A fitness test? - A fitness test?
You must go back to Seoul if you fail it.
Gosh, I can't let that happen.
But it's called the Fun Run. Why a fitness test?
- You can pass it then. - Right. That can't happen.
Right. We'll go to the spot for your fitness test.
- Okay. - Yes.
Guys, don't run.
(They head out for the fitness test.)
(They follow the crew chief down the stairs.)
This is the Chotdae Rock I told you about earlier.
- I see. - It's over there.
- Yes, that one. - It looks like a candlestick.
- That's so cool. - Beautiful, right?
- The East Sea is so pretty. - Yes.
You know what? I knew it.
No one said we should start running.
This is great.
I hate over-the-top people who suggest running right away.
Right.
(They come down as if they're on a walk.)
There's the restroom.
- Do you want to go? - Yes, I need to.
Go ahead.
You let them do whatever they want.
- I'll be back. - Go ahead.
- Go on. - The restroom.
If you need to use it, go ahead.
He shouldn't have run.
So not running is one of the rules?
Right. Don't run unless it's part of the route.
- Unless it's part of the route? - Right.
If you need to use it, go ahead.
- If you want food, join me then. - I want...
If you smell food, eat.
- You didn't even start running. - Why are you eating now?
You started eating already?
But it was really nice to run after some food.
- I was so happy. - See? Ji Hyeon liked that.
Actually, I like this run.
- This is good, right? I like it. - I can handle it. I like it.
- We should have some food. - Gosh.
What's this? This looks good.
(Tender, bouncy squid, roasted on hot stones)
- That looks good. - You must get squid there.
Right. That's a must.
(Salivating)
Try this now.
(They have a taste under the crew chief's guidance.)
(Munching)
(Satisfied)
- Dowoon should eat a lot. - Right, he should eat some.
Dowoon.
- We came here for a run. - Dowoon.
Ji Hyeon.
Please speak casually to me. Seriously.
Then you should too.
I'll do that then.
I like keeping a casual vibe with my juniors.
(Dropping the honorifics in front of the squid)
Come. Try it.
(Dowoon has a bite too.)
I like this Fun Run.
Look how happy he is.
- Fishcakes. - I love it.
It's on me. Have whatever you want.
(The crew chief is buying them fishcakes.)
You can finally see and enjoy these things when you pause.
Exactly.
You should be the PR guy for our crew.
- Sure. - Great.
(Feeling bitter)
Let's go now.
We should get going now. It's a running crew after all.
When will we do the fitness test?
We'll take a taxi.
- A taxi? What? - That's...
- What? - Why are you taking a taxi?
- Why? What? - I have a planned route.
- There's a route for the run. - People usually run there.
We don't.
Are you crazy? Why would we run there?
You'll run today, right?
We will.
Okay.
(They take a taxi to the test site.)
(Oh, my.)
What did you do to your wrist? Did you wear compression bandages?
It's not that. I put on the hand massage device.
It lasted like that for three hours.
This will last six hours.
- It looks like... - Pillow marks last six hours too.
(Pitying)
- You don't get it, right? - They last a long time.
What year were you born?
Weren't you born in the 80s?
- Like 1988? - Or were you born in the 70s?
- No, right? - What did you think?
- Don't look it up. - Weren't you born in 1984?
- He thought I was Kian84's age. - In 1984?
In 1984? That makes no sense.
- "That makes no sense." - "That makes no sense."
- Let me explain. - Hey.
- There's no way. - Don't look it up.
- Then he's too young. - No. What do you think?
Go with your gut.
"Jun Hyun Moo's age."
(Shocked)
You were born in 1977?
Really? You look so young for your age.
- Really? Thank you. - He does look young.
Thank you, Dowoon.
I love you.
(The 18-year-older guy is in a good mood.)
It felt great.
It felt amazing.
(Love is riding on this taxi.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Come over here.
The cherry blossoms aren't in bloom yet.
Is it because it's colder here? Or did the petals already fall?
- I think they fell. - They fell.
It's colder here.
(A verdant trail by the Jeoncheon River)
This place looks beautiful too.
So far, this is just my kind of run.
- I guess I felt... - We should keep it going.
- a bit of pressure about running. - I see.
- Don't feel pressured. - Okay.
Everyone looks so happy.
- Right? - Yes.
What's this place?
- This is the test site? - We'll do the test here.
You guys should've met up in Jamsil.
The air is different.
(Welcome to the park.)
Why would we do the test here?
He's going to test our walking ability.
- Let's do three sets each. - Okay.
Do three sets each.
I wanted to know their basic level of fitness.
I was going to change the route to a shorter one...
if some of them weren't in shape.
- What should we start with? - Let's start with the chest press.
- Okay. - Okay.
Who wants to go first?
- I'll go first. - Okay.
My gosh. I have to pass the test.
- Let's do 3 sets of 10 repetitions. - Okay.
- Three sets of ten repetitions? - Ten?
Wait. Is this the grip?
He doesn't work out, I guess.
That's it.
Two, three,
- He's good. - four. There you go.
- Why work out the arms for running? - Five. That's it.
Seven, eight. Your form looks good.
Nine, ten.
Okay. Stop. That's it. You pass.
(You pass.)
- Wait. He passed? - He passed.
- He already passed? - Your form has to be good.
(Here comes the next applicant.)
One, two. There you go. Three.
- Square your shoulders. - You're good.
Nine, ten. Stop. You also pass.
(Here's the second guy to pass, just seconds later.)
The fitness test for the Fun Run...
Was that really necessary?
- Come on. - Even an elementary school kid...
can pass it.
Age or gender wouldn't matter.
As long as you're healthy, anyone can pass.
The initiation test was...
It was just a formality.
- That's it. He was honest about it. - It's just a fancy formality.
(The formality continues.)
(You're up next, Na Ra.)
- Any plans to change your pants? - No.
Let me try.
(He sits down without changing his pants.)
One,
- two... - Gosh.
- His form is nice. Great. - Yes, look at his form.
He must work out diligently.
Nice. It's nice and firm.
- It's firm, right? - Yes.
(Slapping)
Seven, eight, nine, ten.
Stop. You also pass.
- It's better than not having one. - Right.
(Taking a bite)
What?
What's that?
- Hold on. - You're eating again? What?
- Ji Hyeon brought rice balls. - Yes.
- It had spicy octopus inside. - Okay.
- Was it spicy octopus and pork? - Yes, spicy octopus and pork.
- It was so good. - It was really tasty.
People might think that you're running a full marathon.
If you run at least 10km after all this, you have my respect.
- I see. - Of course, we'll run.
- If you run at least 10km. - We didn't go there to have fun.
(I have a plan for the Fun Run.)
It's so good.
(Humming in approval)
- It was so good. - It looks good.
It does look good.
(Salivating)
(Humming)
- Is it good? - The filling...
It's so good.
It was cold, but it was tastier.
- Of course. - He's the octopus expert.
He is.
- The sauce was perfect. - You're from Mokpo.
Yes.
Listen while you eat.
Okay.
I prepared unique completion certificates.
Like what?
I don't give out plain completion certificates.
- I got you practical certificates. - Practice certificates?
Are you ready to be moved?
- Yes. - Yes.
I made them myself.
Really?
It took me four hours.
- What? - What is it?
Really?
(Handing it over)
What? A vest?
- One, two, three. - Three.
What? What is it?
(What is the completion certificate Moomoo made himself?)
(Crew chief takes out the completion certificate.)
- What is it? - A vest?
- One, two, three. - Three.
- What's this? - Moo Do Ra Ji.
(Welcome to the 1st Fun Run.)
- Each drawing is different. - Yes.
I drew them with love for the crew members.
(Their eyes go wide.)
What a nice artwork.
I drew your face.
Hold on. Is this me?
Is this me?
You recognized yourself right away.
(Ji)
(Ji Hyeon)
How did you find your face right away?
I really don't like this.
(I really don't like this.)
Didn't you squish his face too much?
- That's... - His nose is a triangle.
I laugh every time I look at it.
My artwork is a success when the recipient gets mad.
I'm annoyed because it resembles me a bit.
Ji Hyeon, I'm sorry,
- but I see the resemblance. - Right.
- The details are the same. - That's right.
If you don't like it, how did you find your face right away?
Hold on. Let me take a look.
(Let me take a proper look.)
- Did you draw it yourself? - Yes, I did.
- I'm touched. Seriously. - So this is me.
This is Moo chewy cookie.
That's my face.
He looks like Bruce Lee with long hair.
(Bruce Lee with long hair, Dowoon)
What? Isn't this Ito Junji's artwork?
Seriously.
That's Na Ra.
(Ghost Na Ra)
The hardest thing to draw...
is a handsome face.
I bet it was hard to draw all of us.
- No, Dowoon was the hardest. - Really?
Ji Hyeon was the easiest.
(Laughing)
- Why? Ji Hyeon is handsome. - It's fascinating...
because the drawings carry our vibes.
I drew Ji Hyeon first.
His face stretches sideways when he smiles.
- I see the resemblance. - Totally.
- I see the resemblance. - That's right.
Na Ra's face is characterized by its length.
(Na Ra's face is characterized by its length.)
He is like a cucumber.
A cucumber or a bitter melon.
Dowoon's face has no distinguishing characteristics.
- Dowoon is like that. - That means...
- he is handsome. - He is hard to draw.
So I drew the most handsome face I could think of.
- I know what you mean. - I see the characteristics.
You have skills.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
It's a functional fabric.
It's really nice.
The name of the team is Moo Do Ra Ji from now on.
- Moo Do Ra Ji. - What do you think it means?
- Hyun Moo, Dowoon, - Dowoon,
- Na Ra, Ji Hyeon. - Na Ra, Ji Hyeon.
(Doraji, doraji)
(Moo Do Ra Ji)
That's the team chant of the day.
- Understood? - Okay.
The back represents the Fun Run.
This side is pretty.
- Is it pretty? - It's pretty.
- It's very pretty. - Yes.
I see.
The back side is pretty.
I want that T-shirt.
- Hyun Moo made preparations. - He did a good job.
(Staring)
I prepared them with care. To make it absorb the sweat...
- Today... - Is he looking at his face?
Why did you draw my mouth so big?
I want you to smile always.
- It weighed on Ji Hyeon. - Yes.
All right.
(Wearing)
- This face... - It's pretty.
- That's right. It's pretty. - It looks good.
- Yes. - It suits him.
- It's better than I expected. - All of them are fit.
- Yes. - Thank you.
It took me 20 minutes to draw Ji Hyeon.
Seriously.
To be honest, I really don't like it.
(To be honest, I really don't like it.)
Why? You look cute.
(When he looks at it again,)
(he can only laugh.)
Ji Hyeon is so cute when he does that.
Why do I look like this? Seriously.
(Why do I look like this? Seriously.)
I don't look that ugly. I really don't.
To be completely honest, I really liked it.
What?
It's natural to mock your close friend, right?
Hyun Moo hadn't done that to me before.
But today, he mocked me thoroughly with his drawing.
It made me go, "I became very close to Hyun Moo."
- I was very happy. - My goodness.
Ji Hyeon hated it.
Ji Hyeon wouldn't be happy, but it looked very similar to him.
(It looked very similar to him.)
- No, it's pretty. - Really?
- It's pretty. - It's pretty.
Hyun Moo, what are those under my eyes?
They're beginning to voice their complaints.
It's time for you to get that under-eye fat transfer.
It's so funny that every component has a meaning.
Under-eye fat transfer?
I'll hook you up with a clinic.
(Well...)
I got it done.
Did you get it done?
- Really? - I got it done.
- Hey. - Some people get it done twice.
- You can get it done twice. - Yes.
- Did the fat come back? - Please introduce me to a clinic.
- I'll do that for real. - Okay.
- You hadn't told anyone back then. - No.
I found out just now.
- I bet it hurt his feelings. - That's so funny.
I know.
Okay.
- Are you ready to run? - Yes.
That's good.
(Let's take a group photo.)
(The official induction photo of the Fun Run Crew's 1st batch)
Okay.
Let's run.
Shall we go?
- Let's go. - That sounds good.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hyun Moo. - Why do you keep taking a taxi?
I spent a lot of money for the taxi rides.
(Covering his eyes)
The scenery on the right is so beautiful.
- Isn't it incredible? - Yes.
It would've been better...
to take a bus or something.
- No. - When did it start going wrong?
We're at the Eodal Beach.
- Eodal Beach? - It's a beautiful place.
It's a beautiful place indeed.
- It's so beautiful. - Thank you.
- While running... - Guys.
The supermarket sells iced coffee.
- Let's go. - Let's drink coffee.
- How cute! - You're so cute.
- You're like the owner. - Hello.
- How cute! - Hello.
Go ahead and drink something.
Thank you.
- Everything is on me today. - Thank you.
Chief is someone who pays for many things.
- Of course. - You're right.
My goodness.
Aren't you Jun Hyun Moo?
Hello.
- Oh, my. Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Hold on.
- It's Jun Hyun Moo. - No way!
- My goodness. - Oh, my.
- Oh, my. Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Hold on.
- It's Jun Hyun Moo. - No way!
- You didn't know. - Didn't you know that it was me?
I had no idea.
Gosh, it's Jun Ji Hyun! I mean, Park Ji Hyeon.
Jun Ji Hyun.
(Jun Ji Hyun?)
- Jun Ji Hyun! - Park Ji Hyeon.
- I get that at times. - Really?
- I'm Jun Ji Hyun. - Hurry up and take a photo.
If our names are combined, it’s Jun Ji Hyun.
Jun Hyun Moo and Park Ji Hyeon.
- Jun Ji Hyun. - My goodness.
- Thank you. - Bye.
- We'll come back after a run. - Okay.
- May we leave our belongings here? - Sure.
- Anywhere is fine. - Shall we do that?
- They aren't valuables. - May we leave ours here as well?
Sure. You can leave them here. You can give them to me.
What's this, Hyun Moo? What's this?
(Taking out)
Take one each.
Is it a poop bag?
(No way.)
- What? - You're an adult.
Why would it be a poop bag?
- Why are you giving this to me? - I want to try something.
- What is it? - It's popular these days.
- No way. - Do you know what it is?
One, two, three.
- Butter run. - Butter run. Okay.
- Butter run. - Butter run?
- How could you not know it? - Butter run.
What's a butter run?
When you run with a bag of cream,
- Okay. - it becomes butter.
- You churn it as you run. - That's right.
I've never heard of it.
- Butter run. - Haven't you heard of it?
- No. - I see.
True runners don't know it. They have no interest in it.
You'll need to run a lot to churn it into butter.
You usually need to run about 10km.
- You carry it like this. - It's like a baton.
(They put cream in a zipper bag.)
- Does it need to be shaken? - That's right.
I went on a puppy run before, right?
- That's right. - Puppy run.
Does the East Sea remind you of any animals?
- Squid? - Squid.
Squid? Snow crab?
It doesn't have any legs.
(Here is a hint.)
(Let's go)
(To the East Sea)
- What's this song? - "Whale Hunting."
- Whale. - It's a whale run.
- Whale run. - Whale run.
- Whale? - Whale.
Whale.
(Today's Fun Run is a whale run.)
We'll shape a whale from its tail and move toward its back.
I thought it through.
- Hyun Moo, I have GPS as well. - That's incredible.
- You do? - Yes.
I trust you to help me. I have it all set up.
After a puppy run, the concept is a whale run.
The idea of the puppy run I did last time was from someone else.
This time, I looked up the popular cafes and restaurants...
near the Mukho Beach by the East Sea.
Whales represent the East Sea.
When I connected the places, the shape resembled a whale.
- Did you come up with it? - I came up with it.
- For real? - Yes.
I registered the copyright just in case.
(I registered the copyright.)
I registered the copyright,
so DM me if you want to do a whale run.
You do everything...
- including the uniforms. - Of course.
- But they haven't run yet. - They don't run.
- Exactly. When will they run? - We do everything but run.
The first place is Eodal Port that's popular among Gen Zers.
- Eodal has become popular. - Yes, it has.
We'll begin at the Eodal Intersection.
Then we'll go all the way to the lighthouse...
and come back to the main road.
Then our track will look like a whale's spout.
(A whale's spout)
Right?
As we run along the beach, we'll shape a whale's back.
(A whale's back)
Then we'll go down to complete a whale's head.
Then we'll come back...
to the Eodal Intersection and complete the tail.
- Then it'll roughly shape a whale. - That's the tail.
You'll start from the tail and come back.
- It looks good. - It looks like a whale, right?
It's about 11km in total.
We may get lost, so I think it'll be about 12km.
It'll be great if it takes about an hour and ten minutes.
When I heard about a whale run,
I wondered what the map would look like...
after we completed the run.
When I was young, I was pretty good at running.
And judging by Hyun Moo's makeup,
- Makeup. - I doubt the run will be bad.
I think it'll be pretty easy.
Of course, I'm certain that I'll run well.
This is the Fun Run,
so there isn't too much pressure.
You feel pressured when you run for real.
You need to complete the run in a set amount of time.
- That doesn't apply to us. - You need to stay with the group.
As someone who loves running,
I'm determined to enjoy today's run...
more than anyone.
Look at his facial expression.
I couldn't wait to run.
Really?
- The truth is coming out. - That was how I felt.
Na Ra is one of us.
He is a true runner.
(Eodal Intersection, lighthouse, community service center)
(Fun Run Crew's 1st batch, Moo Do Ra Ji begins the whale run.)
- Let's go. They're starting now. - They're running now.
Now, let's complete the tail.
(They begin with the whale's tail.)
All right.
(Eodal Intersection)
- How about this pace? - Okay.
This was my pace for the last Fun Run.
Hold on. Is that running?
- They aren't running. - Dowoon is speed walking.
- No. - Are they running?
They aren't running.
It's different from a regular run.
- It's different, right? - Yes.
Slowly.
- Is this okay? - Yes, it's great.
Isn't it great?
(Meanwhile, Na Ra isn't satisfied with the speed.)
I wanted to run fast.
You wanted to run properly.
Na Ra kept bouncing up and down.
- He wanted to run. - Yes.
- He is trying to make butter. - Yes.
- He is responsible. - He is shaking the bag.
If you're exhausted, tell me.
If your feet or knees hurt,
- suggest that we take a break. - Okay.
Then we'll take a break right away.
You adjust to the person who is struggling the most.
That's right. We don't worry about the record.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- What? - Who is that?
- They're shouting, "Let's go!" - Who are cheering us on?
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- What's this sound? - What?
There they are.
They're children.
Thanks. We're runners.
- Children. - We're Moo Do Ra Ji.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(They hurriedly run to the cheering children.)
- Children cheered us on. - Let's go!
- Hello. - Hello.
Hi.
Let's go!
- Hi. - How cute!
There is a bit of an incline.
- It's an uphill. - There is an incline as well.
- It's an uphill. - That place has a hill.
- Hello. - Hi.
(Screaming)
They're screaming. My goodness.
Hyun Moo, high-five.
All right.
I did it!
A child followed him easily.
He ran faster than Hyun Moo.
(He outran Hyun Moo easily.)
(Running fast)
(Glancing over)
Hyun Moo, this is a nice pace.
- This is the pace. - Yes.
- What's this pace? - It's nine minutes per kilometer.
- Nine minutes. - I've shortened the time a lot.
It's suitable for the Fun Run.
(The 1st Fun Run was full of ambitions.)
(The pace was 12 minutes and 55 seconds per kilometer.)
(He shortened the time by 3 minutes. It's a big progress.)
- It's an uphill. - An uphill?
Is it an uphill?
It's an uphill.
An uphill?
(It's too cute to be an uphill.)
- An uphill! - An uphill!
You'll feel it in your muscles.
(They join forces to overcome the uphill.)
Are you struggling already?
(Doraji, doraji)
(Moo Do Ra Ji)
(He is moved by the crew members' chant.)
I'm sweating.
Are you serious?
It was a bit cold that day.
- Was it cold? - Was it chilly?
But he was sweating.
Aren't you sweating?
(Despite the cold weather, Na Ra enjoys himself as he sweats.)
I'm breaking into a sweat.
You're sweating.
- There is sweat on your philtrum. - Yes.
(That's good.)
- I'm sweating. - It's too...
I'm breaking into a sweat.
Hyun Moo, I guess this isn't hard for you.
I don't feel like I've done anything.
(Laughing)
You wouldn't expect it, but Hyun Moo has incredible stamina.
- Seriously. - I think you're right.
I'm the frontrunner of the Fun Run.
(It's easy for the frontrunner of the Fun Run.)
(Smiling)
- It's harder than I thought. - I told you so.
You're running with your core strength.
Don't your knees feel stable?
- I love it. - Right?
I see that taping works.
It really works.
How are your knees?
- Thank goodness for taping. - Yes.
- They feel stable. - Thank goodness.
(Dowoon waddles by himself.)
Look at Dowoon. His form is a mess.
Because you're the leader,
- your form is the prettiest. - Right?
MINHO approved of my form.
(I shouldn't have said anything.)
If we run 10km like this,
it won't be half bad.
Dowoon, you'll be running more than you usually do.
It's your 1st time running 10km, right?
That's right.
It's really nice...
to have a good time with good people.
- What a nice comment! - Yes!
(What a nice comment!)
We've run 1km.
- Have we run 1km? - Yes.
It hasn't taken long.
- We've run 1km. - Seriously.
- We're nearly there. - We're nearly there.
Not much distance remains.
(Moo Do Ra Ji is full of positive energy.)
We're back at the base camp.
(We're back at the base camp.)
We're setting off after completing the tail.
- We drew both sides... - Okay.
of the tale.
That's good.
- We completed the tale. - You're right. It's a triangle.
- All right. - Is it this way?
Do you want to go this way or that way?
(Glancing over)
(To their left is a steep incline.)
(To their right is a flatland with the ocean view.)
Do you want to go this way or that way?
(1. Uphill, 2. Flatland)
(The two opposites)
That's a total uphill.
Since it's the Fun Run, there shouldn't be an uphill.
- I agree with you. - Yes.
You shouldn't walk there.
Shouldn't you go up the hill while you have the strength?
Do you want to go this way or that way?
(Moo Do Ra Ji is torn.)
Shall we go that way?
Then we'll go downhill on our way back.
- Na Ra, you want to go this way. - Yes.
Shall we go this way?
- Let's go this way. - It's the popular choice.
Let's go.
(Flatland gets a unanimous vote.)
We don't go uphill.
It's another rule of the Fun Run.
You walk when there is a staircase or an uphill.
That's the line we don't cross.
If we run in such cases,
it won't be fun.
It'll be annoying.
What's the point of having a fit body...
when your feelings are hurt?
- What a great saying. - Feelings!
Let's complete the back of the whale.
- Okay. - The back.
- It's nice. - Yes.
- The weather is really nice. - I know.
You'll feel very proud after completing the run.
Your circulation will be better.
It looks like Na Ra wants to run faster.
Kian84, I'm sure you know this.
You work out your legs...
- by jogging... - Okay.
- before running properly. - That's right.
When you do that, you want to run fast.
- You get that urge. - Yes. You get that urge...
when your legs are ready.
Why did you ask him, not your leader?
He asked a true runner.
- When you're a true runner, - Listen.
you'll want to run fast.
Why did you ask him,
- not your leader? - I'm sorry.
He naturally said to Kian84, "I'm sure you know this."
You're a fake runner.
You didn't think that I'd know.
- It's really refreshing. - It's refreshing indeed.
(A refreshing Fun Run with the chief)
The water is clear.
My goodness.
- The East Sea is... - Yes?
much cleaner.
- Really? - Yes.
It'll be less exhausting since they can enjoy the view.
It's nice.
(One step at a time along the East Sea)
- We'll go this way to outline... - Okay.
the whale's spout.
- My goodness. - It'll shoot out water.
(Pow)
(Glancing over)
"I'm always on your side."
"I'm always on your side" sounds like a trot song title.
- I know. - I'm always on your side
It's atmospheric.
Let's go.
- An uphill! - An uphill!
(They run uphill.)
I can smell the sea.
(The place where the blue dream of the East Sea shimmers)
(They get a nice view of the East Sea.)
This place is so pretty.
- I know. - This place.
Look at the red lighthouse.
It's so pretty.
- Let's make a U-turn. - A U-turn.
A U-turn.
(Let's take a photo.)
(Gathering around)
- My goodness. - Everyone is up for a photo.
- I feel happy. - Do you feel happy?
Yes. I love that...
- there is no pressure. - Nice.
I could enjoy a run like this...
- anytime. - I know.
(It's nice!)
I was worried that the run would leave me out of breath.
It was really nice. I loved the pace.
Okay.
(I love that we aren't going fast!)
(Happy)
Let's go and outline the back.
- The back. - Let's go.
(After completing the spout, they move on to the back.)
- It's just right. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
We're Moo Do Ra Ji.
- Have a nice day. - Please give us a lot of love.
- We're Moo Do Ra Ji. - My goodness.
We're a new male idol group.
(Doraji, doraji)
(Moo Do Ra Ji)
(Doraji)
(Doraji, Moo Do Ra Ji)
You have no choice but to sing along.
(Fallen for the Fun Run without realizing it)
(Fun Run's 1st Crew)
(Moo Do Ra Ji)
Let's go!
- Eodal. - Eodal.
The energy level is really high.
- That's amazing. - They're feeling great right now.
On the other side of the road,
there's a really good cold raw fish soup place.
- You should've told us. - It's really small.
- It's the smallest place. - Those places serve great food.
After driving in from the city,
you'll find Mukho Beach.
Take a left and park there. It will be right behind.
That place serves really good food.
Would you like to come for the second Fun Run?
- I don't enjoy moving. - We can't join.
(We don't like moving.)
- With a pleasant heart, - We will show you our support.
we will show you our support.
- Let's go, Fun Run! - Let's go!
- Yes! - Yes!
Just tell us where the good restaurants are.
(Good restaurants will be shared with the Fun Eat crew.)
This is a famous cafe.
- Really? - It's a bakery as well.
Would you not like to go to the famous cafe?
- Will we pass it? - Shall we go?
- Let's go right away. - Let's go.
As you wish. Let's vote.
- Let's see. - Will we go or not?
- Let's go! - Okay!
You're all laughing.
- We must visit a famous place. - We're laughing all the time.
This is part of the Fun Run.
- Look at all the people. - Right.
So they take a break every 3km.
That's around the 3km mark.
It smells amazing.
Right. They use good butter.
- The bakery! - What's going on?
They all went to have some bread in my opinion.
(The tray is filled with bread even though they ate earlier.)
Based on my research,
the whale's back side has more...
delicious places than the belly side.
So there's nothing to eat after passing the back.
That would be a total miss.
That isn't fun.
We must eat all we can before passing the back.
We must visit the places that are famous and crowded.
Isn't it nice to take a break in the middle?
- It's really nice. - Why must we run until we...
- smell the blood inside of us? - Right.
We can take a break when it's slightly exhausting.
- It's perfect right now. - It's perfect, isn't it?
We shouldn't be smelling the blood inside of us.
That must be bad for us, don't you think?
I feel great right now.
- Right. - Right.
This might be a healthier way.
(Eyes opening wide)
Hey!
(How is the butter?)
(Eyes opening wide)
Hey!
- What is it? Is it ready already? - Is it ready?
Gosh! It's ready.
- The butter is ready. - It looks like kaymak.
It really became a thick texture.
Gosh, you really ran your best.
- How did it become like this? - I kept shaking it.
The butter is ready.
I saw Na Ra in a different light.
He's a guy with a great sense of responsibility.
Even if he were to be an office worker,
I believe he would become really successful.
"Did you decide to start the Butter Run?"
"Yes. I must make some butter, Director Jun." Like this.
He's a great guy.
I would've really adored him if I were his superior.
That was what I thought to myself.
- Right. - Mine hasn't changed.
You have to shake it as you run.
It needs to be moved around, right?
- Right. It has to be shaken. - Okay.
- Okay. - Right. It has to be shaken.
- Nice! - It looks really good!
Gosh, this place is amazing.
- Should I squeeze out the butter? - Give it a try.
- I'll place it here. - Right.
He did a great job.
- I'll place it here. - We're in France right now.
How did it become like that?
It's perfect.
(Drooling)
Would you like some on top?
(A generous amount of handmade butter)
- Gosh, it's fresh butter. - This butter...
- It looks delicious. - Give it a try.
(Impressed)
(How is it?)
I feel like I'm in Montmartre right now.
(It's time to say, "Bonjour.")
Is it good?
- I realized why people do this. - Really?
- Is it good? - It's good.
- You should try some as well. - Go ahead.
You made a lot as well.
- Go ahead. - Give it a try.
- It looks good, doesn't it? - What's this one?
The salt bread.
It's good, isn't it?
It's good.
It's nice. This is really fascinating.
- It was really fascinating. - It looks good.
- You're having it properly. - Gosh, he's enjoying it.
- How did it taste? - It looks really good.
It was incredibly savory.
This is really nice. Gosh.
Didn't my saliva get on your bread?
- It's fine. I can eat it up. - No?
Hey!
The two got close now.
- They're much closer now. - They're connected now.
- Exercising together helps. - Right.
- Sweating together... - Sweating together...
makes people get close together.
(Sipping)
Is it good?
It's good. Try it with the cream.
(Sipping)
It's good.
I love the first crew of the Fun Run.
I really do.
(Peeking)
I worked with my father in the past...
to make some doenjang jjigae.
- I feel full now. - Hold on, Ji Hyeon.
- Thank you. - He's sweet.
- You're so sweet. - You're good now.
Shall we get going now, Hyun Moo?
Why leave so early?
(Joking)
- They feel a lot closer now. - Right.
We had a great start together.
The guys were all favorable.
If one of them showed a negative response,
it would've affected us.
But none of them said no to anything.
"Let's go! Sounds good!"
"This is fun!" They all cheered each other up.
It was the exact atmosphere that I wished for.
It's comfortable to watch as none of them seem to feel stressed out.
Same here.
- It's comfortable to watch. - It's comfortable to watch.
(They set off again after filling their stomachs.)
Uphill!
Are you sure you're going uphill?
(Embarrassed)
(Doraji, doraji)
(Moo Do Ra Ji)
(They manage to go uphill while singing the Moo Do Ra Ji song.)
When the Moo Do Ra Ji song was sung,
- it happened to bring up my energy. - Right.
- These chants are really important. - Right.
- Hello. - Hello.
- We're Moo Do Ra Ji. - Hello.
We're a new trot group.
(It's great to see you.)
We could get sick if we run too fast.
Take it easy as it might startle our bodies.
This is the perfect speed.
Let's go!
People might think we're finishing a 30km course.
People might think it's a run around the whole country.
Don't give up!
- Don't get exhausted. - Never give up.
- Be unbreakable. - Wear long johns?
Oh, "Never give up."
He thought he was told to wear long johns.
It feels like it's a full-course marathon.
It feels like a long course.
(They head to their destination as if it's a full-course marathon.)
- The back is being made. - Right.
Okay. You see the injeomi place, right?
- Right. - Take a right from there.
(Current location)
Which way do we go now?
Keep going straight.
(They pace forward while following the crew leader's orders.)
- Be careful with your joints. - Be careful with your joints.
Your joints.
(Peeking)
It's quite steep now.
Pace down.
(A steep uphill course appears in front of Moo Do Ra Ji.)
- It's quite long. - It's quite long.
It's long.
The slope was around 2km long.
- Gosh. - Gosh, it's long.
The GPS doesn't show uphill courses.
If there were contour lines,
I would've taken out the head course.
I didn't know that the head course was this steep.
It was really steep.
This was bad judgment on my part, but we had to carry on.
(In front of the Fun Run crew,)
(a steep uphill course that doesn't look fun appears.)
(Panting)
(So Fun Runs have tough times as well.)
(Vivid memories of that moment)
(Shocking and terrifying scenes)
That's terrible.
(What happened to Moo Do Ra Ji?)
(I Live Alone)
(My Partner Forever)
This is going to be fun.
Let's have fun today. Got it?
(Jae Hyeon walks while talking to his bag.)
You're feeling good, right?
Do you want to take a look outside?
Can you see things outside?
- It's raining. Nice, isn't it? - Did you go outside?
It was a while since I went outside with Anju.
You're really blessed for that to happen, Jae Hyeon.
- Why is that? - You're blessed to have...
a cat that can go outside.
What usually happens when you take a cat outside?
Most cats can't be taken outside.
- Right. - Most of them.
- They hate going outside? - They usually won't stay still.
(They usually won't stay still.)
Do the wildcats in your house...
go wild when you take them outside?
- That would be the end of me. - Really?
- Really? - That would be the end of you?
It's our first time, isn't it, Anju?
Anju doesn't go outside often either.
I usually take him outside when we visit the vet.
He's really calm.
- He's really calm. - Right.
Let's go.
(He walks down to the basement.)
- Let's go. - Where is this?
Isn't it the gym?
It doesn't seem like the vet.
(A gym? The vet?)
Where is this place?
Hello.
- I'll check your reservation. - Right.
- Did you book the cinema room? - Is it the vet?
- Right. - Where is this?
You can go inside there.
- It isn't the vet. - Right.
I came to the self-service photo studio with Anju.
It's a photo studio?
It's hard to leave the house with a cat.
I made a big decision to come out with Anju...
to take photos at a self-service photo studio.
Anju is 13 already.
- Gosh, he's quite old. - A cat being 13 years old...
means that it's around 70 years old as a person.
The last family photo I took with Anju...
was during the last Chuseok.
Last Chuseok,
the photo that was taken still gives me nightmares.
(They tried to take family photos in Chuseok before last.)
That was quite a while back.
(He ended up looking like a man who lives alone in Seongsu-dong.)
- It's really scary. - Is it a picture of a ghost?
(Is it a picture of a ghost?)
It looked...
somewhat gloomy.
It didn't feel good enough to be framed.
I did a bad job of taking the photo.
That was bad, wasn't it? It shouldn't be framed, right?
(It shouldn't be framed.)
While browsing online,
I noticed that there were many pet photo studios.
So there are places like that.
I wanted to take good photos with Anju,
and that was why I came to the self-service photo studio.
I made a big decision to leave with Anju after 13 years.
(Amazed)
Gosh.
- Gosh! - It looks nice.
It's a movie theater.
So there are places like this.
I would never be able to go to a movie theater with Anju.
- Right. - Right.
- Right. - That could never happen.
(Items to make it seem like he's watching a movie with Anju)
Gosh, there are so many fascinating places.
- It's a cat, right? - Yes.
- You can take the cat out. - Right.
- Just make sure he doesn't leave. - Right.
If you look here,
- I will explain things for you. - Right.
You will take photos...
- on your own here. - Right.
When you press the button, the photo will be taken.
- The photo will be shown here. - Right.
You will get 20 minutes.
- Right. - I will set the timer here.
Got it.
It's time to come out now, Anju.
Come out!
Come out! Okay.
You're out.
He won't take off the harness. He's really mild.
The fact that he's wearing a harness...
- is a miracle. - Right.
Anju, I brought your cushion.
What do you think?
Hold on.
My arm will be here.
(Looking closely)
Then I should place Anju here.
(He sets Anju's spot after checking the angles.)
The angles are set first.
Anju! Your cushion is here.
He's so mild.
Take a look, Anju.
(He heads toward the cushion he's familiar with.)
- He's just like a dog! - Take a look around.
(Turning)
(He starts to get curious about the place.)
You need some time to look around, don't you, Anju?
(He lets Anju look around to get comfortable with the place.)
The timer might go off while looking around the place.
When will he have the time to take the photos like that?
There you are, Anju!
(Anju pops out his head while looking around.)
What a great owner. So much time is being spent.
But when it comes to the final result,
that would certainly be a wiser way to handle things.
Really?
Let's go.
I checked to see what it would come out like.
Do you find it fascinating?
(Taking a look)
Anju's face isn't showing.
(A test shot to check the angles)
- It was a test shot? - Right.
(So that's what it's like.)
There are glasses here, Anju.
(Being equipped with nice glasses)
He's so cute!
Cats like dark places.
Fortunately, Anju got used to the place fairly quickly.
(Placing down)
(He strikes a pose as a model.)
The model.
There isn't much when taking a photo.
I believe that I will look good...
when my partner looks good.
The kid looks fashionable.
Who? Ahn Jae Hyeon?
- No. - Anju.
No matter how rude I could be,
I would never refer to him as a kid.
(Ahn Jae Hyeon, model with 18 years of experience)
He looks great.
(Photoshoot tips from Model Ahn Jae Hyeon)
First of all, I made the place as a comfortable place like home,
and prepared Anju's favorite cushion.
I brought the toys that Anju likes as well.
That must be done.
You should never look at the camera in a photoshoot.
You would look really awkward when you do that.
(Never make eye contact.)
(The perfect example of eye contact?)
The camera lens is about to get pierced!
All bad examples are from me.
Also,
the photo shouldn't be taken...
so that someone says, "This is Ahn Jae Hyeon?"
- The model shouldn't stand out. - These things must be learned.
We should learn from the model.
It must look natural...
so that the model feels like someone walking by.
That brings the best results.
It looks great on Anju.
I've never heard of that before.
It's a great tip.
(Sticking out here)
(Sticking out there)
I thought that was his front paw.
- He's showing off his paw? - Anju!
You're so cute, Anju!
You make it look really stylish.
He's a true professional.
(Great. Let's keep this going.)
(I'm going to go.)
- He feels irritated now. - Right.
- The time has come. - Right.
- He feels irritated now. - The time has come.
- Right. - When that happens,
it would be hard to calm down the cat.
Hey. Hello.
(Chasing)
(Photos are taken as he follows Anju.)
- It must look natural. - Holding Anju was impossible.
(This is harder than I thought.)
You're so cute!
Right. Look at the camera.
(Looking around)
Anju!
It's hard to make a cat look at the camera.
Right. It's hard to set a direction.
- It's hard to capture that moment. - It's disappointing.
It's hard to take photos with animals.
Someone has to shake something behind the camera.
Right.
Someone else had to get the cat's attention.
It would've been better with one more person.
- That makes things a lot better. - Right.
(Goodbye.)
- Gosh. - It's tough.
(I don't have much time left.)
Anju!
- Didn't he use all the time? - Just one is good enough!
Just one!
Let's see.
(He's covered in sweat.)
- He's sweating that much? - What?
It was hot in there.
It's different in reality. It's definitely different.
My first thought was to make the place feel comfortable...
and to take photos after making Anju feel at home.
The room was much bigger than I thought.
There were many places to hide as well.
- He's always out of the angle. - Right.
- He's always out of the angle. - It's hilarious.
And it was really hot in there.
Why was that?
Well,
last year,
as the Shaka Guy,
I thought that I was reborn as a healthy man.
"Shaka Guy."
Your muscles weren't enough.
Right.
- Gosh. - You look great now.
It was hard for me to watch.
(Joking)
I must've been wrong.
(Even the Shaka Guy struggled with the heat.)
What do I do?
It would be great if you could go up. Right, Anju?
(The first family photoshoot isn't easy.)
It would be great if the two are sitting naturally.
- Right. - There you go!
- Be quick! - Now is the time!
- You have to sit down quickly! - Take it now!
(Now is the time!)
(You have to sit down quickly!)
(Now!)
- You should sit down! - You have to pose as well!
- Why am I being like that? - This is so frustrating.
Gosh, this is frustrating to watch.
- What are you doing? - Siru is doing well!
(Siru is doing well!)
- What? - Siru lives in his house.
- It's Anju. - It's Anju.
- Anju is doing well! - Gosh.
Siru got a compliment!
(Yes!)
- An unexpected compliment. - It has been too long.
(Forgive me.)
(This is a chance.)
(He sits down carefully.)
Anju's pose is perfect right now.
- It's perfect. - It's perfect.
(I feel comfortable.)
- There you go. - There you go.
- It looks great. - It's the perfect angle.
- There you go. - This was the vibe I wanted, Anju.
There are flowers.
(Calm)
I imagined the two of us after renting a whole movie theater.
I wondered how we would play with each other.
I tried a proposal scene as well.
(Proposal scene)
The birthday hat was to represent a birthday party...
at a movie theater after renting there.
That sounds impressive to rent the whole place.
After setting a theme,
it was easier to take the photos.
- He got the hang of it. - With Anju?
So I'm highly satisfied.
(Dignified)
Nice.
Goodness.
You've got even thinner.
- This looks like a ghost photo too. - You look gaunt.
What's wrong with his face?
(The ghost photo returned in the end.)
(The little brother looking radiant)
- He's so handsome. - How pretty.
He's so cute.
- Why is he so... - What's wrong with me?
My goodness.
(Excited)
He poses so well now, right?
(Sweaty)
Gosh, look at all that sweat.
It was tiring.
(It was tiring.)
(Dragging his tired body...)
This is a lot of work.
Ta-da.
(He does his best to take the first official family photo.)
How cute! This is crazy, Anju.
(A large batch of A-cuts salvaged at the end of the shoot)
My wish came true.
I was happy.
That's cool.
Wait.
Time's up.
(He gave it everything.)
Anju, well done.
(Returning to the carrier after doing a good job)
It was more difficult than a magazine photoshoot.
It's meaningful that you took photos like those.
- Anju. - That's right.
That was amazing.
It was fantastic.
I should roll off his fur with a lint roller.
Do you have to clean up after using the space?
They clean it for us, but I did it just in case.
Other people use it too.
(Just in case!)
(After a chaotic photoshoot...)
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
- Great work. Thank you. - Bye.
(Hurrying out with his umbrella)
It's raining.
(Trudging)
Gosh.
Anju, that was fun, right?
You could be a model.
Do you want to become a cat model?
(Do you want to become a cat model, Anju?)
Let's take a taxi.
(I'll think about it.)
Are you happy?
The weather's good?
(Glancing)
(The taxi is here.)
(Let's go.)
- Hello. - Hello, sir.
Sir, it's my first time in a pet taxi.
- Is that so? - Yes.
I see.
It's so nice that there's a pet taxi.
Anju, it feels like it's been forever since we last went out.
(It's been a while since he and Anju went for a drive.)
Anju, today was so much fun, right?
Right?
Yes or no?
I always ask that too.
- Right? - They wouldn't answer, so...
(That's true.)
Don't say anything if you agree.
How cute.
Cats are the cutest in that angle.
Great.
(We're indeed meant to be.)
We're taking an overpass?
(The couple of the century is heading somewhere.)
The cherry blossoms have bloomed too.
It's been a while since we last saw cherry blossoms too.
You're a good cat.
I wonder what cats think while looking out the view.
Right?
It will be perfect if we listen to the rain and take a nap, right?
- It'll be perfect with jazz, right? - You talk to him a lot.
I should.
You talk to him a lot.
- Thank you, sir. - Sure.
Thank you.
(Grunting)
You slept well, didn't you, Anju?
(Going somewhere while asking how Anju was)
You slept well.
We're here.
Where are you?
Hello.
A hospital?
It's not easy to go out with a cat.
- So... - That's right.
I tend to go out and handle all errands at once.
Today is Anju's health checkup day.
He gets a health checkup once a year,
but he's so old,
so he's going to take all the tests he can.
(A full-course health checkup)
- Hello. - Hello.
Oh, my.
There's a cat like you, Anju. Hi.
- Who is this, Anju? - What?
- Gosh, he looks like Anju. - It's Haneul.
How old is Haneul?
- He's around two. - Two?
- He's still a baby. - He's still a baby.
Haneul is so pretty.
(A beautiful cat)
You're here for Anju's health checkup, right?
Yes, Anju is here for his health checkup.
One second, please.
You can go into the doctor's office now.
- Hello, sir. - Hello.
- Have you been well? - Yes. Please come in.
Has Anju been well too?
(He growled every time he was at the hospital.)
Before...
He's on a diet, so...
I can touch his belly.
- That's when he was chubby. - That's right.
He's been doing so well.
Nothing's been stressing him out these days.
(The consultation time is here again.)
He's been eating well too.
I switched from diet pet food...
- to the normal one. - I see.
- He hates to be there. - There, there.
Why does he do that when he's only at the hospital?
You feel bad, don't you?
He must have bad memories regarding it.
Gosh, you're annoyed, aren't you?
You're a cutie.
It looks like he knows the smell of the hospital.
Both animals and humans don't like hospitals.
How are other cats like when they go to the hospital?
The doctors are in crisis...
- when my cats visit. - Really?
Goodness. I understand.
But I feel a little relieved when I see them with their doctor.
- Why? - Because they're active with them.
- The fact that they're energetic. - On the contrary?
Right. You feel bad when you don't see them being energetic.
He must be really happy.
- Anyhow, he's 13 now. - Right.
He's over 60 in human age.
- Right. Like he's in his 70s. - He's around that age.
His kidney is... Right?
- He's always had a problem. - Right.
Also, there was a howling early in the morning.
(He's full of worries even about small things.)
He must've been really gloomy.
- He cried a lot more. - Really?
But first of all...
There are parts I've always paid attention to.
His diet too.
There are things I've been keeping track...
from the first moment I saw him.
Half of me is worried,
but half of me thinks he'll be okay after seeing his condition.
That's what half of me feels.
All sorts of thoughts occurred to me.
He'll be okay since you did well in managing his health.
What kind of medical tests should Anju get today?
- Since he's an old cat, - Yes.
he'll take a general test, a pancreatitis test,
an early heart failure test,
and X-ray.
It really is a comprehensive checkup.
You're a good boy.
After having dinner...
Gosh, you don't like it.
- Gosh, you don't like it. - Oh, no.
You don't feel good?
Gosh, you scared me.
You're like that whenever you're in the hospital.
You're mad.
He can't be happy about it.
Since you're hungry and angry, right?
It'll be over soon.
It'll take around 30 minutes.
- Then I'll wait outside. - All right.
- We'll be back after the exam. - Okay.
Let's go, Anju.
(Going out to test Anju)
(Jae Hyeon is so anxious that he can't even sit.)
(Meowing)
Gosh.
Goodness.
Let's try it first without this.
(Staring at the doctor's office as he's worried about Anju)
- It's going to sting. - Oh, no.
- Oh, no. - Look at his face.
(Not happy)
Gosh, you don't like it.
(Getting his blood tested first)
His blood vessels are thin too.
He's such a good boy.
Gosh, you're good.
But his foot is chubby.
The doctor says things that deserves a scratch.
(Stretching)
(Finding it cute)
An X-ray?
(Getting an X-ray next)
(Crying)
His teeth look fine.
They're fine compared to his age.
All right.
(Checking his eyes too)
They checked his eyes too?
He looks like the next patient waiting.
(The next patient who is anxiously waiting)
He looks even more unwell.
I'm worried.
(I'm worried.)
I was sitting after Anju was sent to the treatment room.
But that 30 minutes went by really slowly.
It goes by longer than you think.
Also, he does it without anesthesia.
I can hear so well how he hisses.
I can hear it so well.
(He feels heavy for no reason.)
It's just a mere healthy checkup.
But in my head, I'm sitting in front of an operating room.
My feeling changes just like that.
(It feels as if he's sitting in front of an operating room.)
(Clicking)
Gosh, I could hear that clicking sound from outside.
(The doctor is checking something.)
He doesn't look too pleased.
I know. Is something wrong?
(Clicking)
Actually, what really scared me...
was the clicking sound of the doctor's mouse.
That clicking sound...
It pressured me so much.
"What? What's he clicking so much?"
As old as Anju was,
it felt more like a warning sound.
I wanted to hear the result as fast as I could.
I wanted to hear the doctor talk.
- I bet you're concerned. - Right.
That means he needs to check various areas.
- Yes, that was it. - That's right.
- It's because he's old. - That's right.
It usually finishes shortly.
(Meanwhile, Jae Hyeon is waiting for the results of Anju's health.)
Come in, please.
- He's so ready for it. - Because you were so worried...
Compared to his physical stamina,
- He was really fast. - he's quick.
Be careful. Your joint will go out.
You're worried, right?
- Doctor... - It's...
We were only trying to look at the examination result in detail.
That's why it took so long.
It took so...
(How is Anju?)
To compare it to the result from the previous one...
(Is Anju okay?)
You've managed him so well.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Compared to others,
his numbers are stable.
- I'm glad. - He's...
Cats tend to hide their diseases.
They may look normal,
but the numbers could be dramatically wrong.
Also, there are times when serious illnesses are found.
For three years,
his numbers haven't changed much.
His numbers are similar to the ones from years ago.
So I'm relieved.
- You took great care of him. - I know.
Also, he's been on a healthy diet.
This is his ab definition.
(Moved)
- The definition. - He lost so much weight.
(2 years ago)
(Anju was 6kg.)
- He was chubby. - He should be on a diet.
How heavy is he now?
Gosh, you're good.
(He lost as much as 1kg.)
If he lost 1kg...
Gosh, he was on a diet?
Still, compared to three years ago,
- the numbers are similar. - Yes, you managed him well.
I'm so glad you managed him so well.
You must've felt so good.
But...
- If you look here... - He said, "But."
He has a lot of tartar on his teeth.
And his gum is overgrown.
(Oh, no.)
Didn't he show discomfort in his left eye recently?
He did.
There's a scratch on his cornea.
You'll need a prescription for that.
You'll need to put eye drops in his eyes.
I think he'll be good as long as his tartar is removed.
- You managed well. - Thank you.
(You managed well.)
(Falling)
I was worried outside.
I thought I was waiting in front of the operating room.
Does he need to get scaling today?
Yes, it'll be good if he does.
- All right. - Okay.
- Gosh, how do you do it? - How does he get one?
That means the doctor will get scratched a hundred times.
Take a look at your baby one last time.
- Take a look at him one last time. - Please, sir.
(His heart sinks.)
- That sounded strange. - Gosh.
Anju.
To put an eye drop.
The color near his eyes turned out that way because of it.
It looks like he put on eye makeup.
Let's go home after getting your teeth cleaned.
It's because you had a lot of Churu treats.
You can hang out with Haneul when you're done.
What do you think? Do you want to hang out with Haneul?
All right. Let's hang out with Haneul.
- How cute. - Please take good care of him.
(I'll be out after brushing my teeth.)
- He's upset. - Yes, he is.
He's upset. Ae Ong got upset when I took him to hospitals.
- They get upset. - How cute.
(He comes out after leaving Anju to clean his teeth.)
Haneul.
You got a healthy and old friend.
What do you say to a healthy old grandpa?
It has no interest in the world.
It must've seen so many different kinds of customers.
Everyone who talks to him.
- "Haneul." - Everyone would talk to him.
He'd be like, "He's like others."
He must be sick and tired.
Do you want a doll?
- Gosh. - He must be sick of it.
"A customer before did."
(Sorry)
(Laughing)
Gosh, I feel proud that I took good care of him.
The doctor said I took good care of Anju.
I bet those who have cats know.
There are many times...
when we spend time with each other as if we don't live together.
"Did you eat?" It's something like this.
So, it's not like I took good care of him.
It's that Anju lived well and put up with everything well.
I think that's more right.
Gosh, I'm happy.
I'm glad.
(I'm glad.)
Anju must come first before anything.
Yes, he does.
- Gosh. - Is he crying?
(Is he crying?)
- His eyes were teary. - This breed tends to.
He's like a human.
(Cute)
(Crying)
- He must hate it. - He must.
Even humans hate it when getting their teeth cleaned.
It was because it was almost time to go home.
(Looking gaunt)
Oh, no.
- The doctor... - The doctor is...
(Before and after teeth cleaning)
(He looks a lot gaunter.)
He should get his health checked up.
- I just noticed that he sweated. - I mean...
Gosh, he went through a lot.
- He had to go through a lot. - I'm so grateful.
(Looking gaunt)
(He's done with teeth cleaning.)
Goodness. Let's go.
He wants to send him away quickly.
He must've been exhausted.
(Growling)
Did you?
- Thank you. - Thank you, doctor.
Anju. Let's go home.
I should take my cat to the hospital once too.
Anju, you went through a lot.
It must've hurt you so much.
It hurt a lot, didn't it?
You must've felt so relieved.
- Totally. I was so relieved. - Right.
They said he was healthy, so...
Shall we take a nap at home?
(He quickly got home for Anju who must've been tired.)
We're home, Anju.
Anju, well done.
Gosh, my baby.
My dear.
My baby.
Gosh, my baby.
- He's happy. - My gosh.
- It's like paradise. - Goodness.
- Gosh, it was hard, wasn't it? - He took it off right away.
He did.
- You're hungry, aren't you? - He's hungry.
He went to his bowl right away.
You must've been hungry.
- He went to his bowl. - You were hungry.
(Cute)
Anju. I know. You must've been through a lot.
"Give me food instead of touching me."
You're right. He's doing that for food.
Let me wash my hands and use the bathroom.
(Give me food before you go.)
Look at his face. It's like he's saying, "Should I kill him?"
(Sorry)
You must be hungry.
(Jae Hyeon quickly washed his hands for Anju.)
Anju, come here.
Come here. It's time for food.
(It's food!)
He must've been hungry.
Eat slowly.
(Worried)
You must've been hungry. Goodness.
(Eating in a hurry)
You're eating well. It's good.
Anju, it's good, isn't it?
Eat slowly.
(Anju eats well without lifting his head even once.)
He ate so excitedly.
You've been managing good health for three years straight.
(Feeling proud)
Anju.
They said you were incredible.
He's indeed tall.
(Watching Anju while stretching his long legs)
I think the foundation of life is eating well.
So seeing Anju eat well...
made me so happy.
I was so glad he ate well.
So it made me watch Anju eat well after a long while.
Healthy cat.
(Knocking)
What? Someone's here?
It's my food!
He must've ordered something.
Thank you.
(What is it?)
Anju.
My food is here.
(Approaching)
(Excited)
- It smells so good. - Chicken?
It's a chicken burger.
Gosh, I'm starved.
Gosh, it's huge.
(Taking a big bite after taking care of Anju)
(Exclaiming)
(Nodding)
It must be good.
It's good.
This is the chicken burger?
(His appetite came back naturally.)
(Skillfully deboning)
It looks good.
(Drooling)
I'm so full.
- He finished it. - You finished one?
I did. It was good.
I'm so happy.
Anju, let's check out the photos.
- The highlight of the day. - Opening!
(Excited)
Oh, my!
- What is it? - What is it?
They turned it into a keychain?
It's so cute. Anju. This is amazing.
Look. What do you think?
(Turning)
Really? Check it out after you eat.
Oh, my.
It feels different when it's printed.
Gosh, it's really hip.
(A proper family photo taken after 13 years)
Oh, my. Anju. Look.
I'm sorry when you're eating. Look, Anju.
(I'm sorry to bother you when you're eating, but look.)
Look.
All right.
(Okay. Eat first.)
Anju, look.
Look. You're being proposed. What do you think?
Anju. Look.
Anju. I chose nine photos.
(Uninterested)
Anju. Look.
Somehow, I feel...
Anju and I are one step apart.
When I look for him, he isn't in front of me.
But he's always watching me from behind.
(Anju always watches me from behind.)
That's how it felt. So...
It was just...
I wish he'll always be there for me.
I know.
I wish he'll be my friend who always welcomes me home.
There was a time when Anju was really young.
Gosh, he's so small.
He's a friend whom we've spent 13 years with.
It was a day when memories came back one by one.
He's a friend and a brother...
I love the most...
and a shadow who can't be separated from me.
(He's my shadow who's always with me.)
He's become my family.
Anju must feel the same way toward you.
- That's right. - Thank you so much, Ji Hyeon.
If I were to say something to Anju,
I'd tell him, "Stay with me for a long time."
I've shared that Ange means fairy in French.
Anju, you're my fairy.
And lastly, I love you, Anju.
(I love you, Anju.)
It's a little sad. Time goes really fast for cats and dogs.
You don't want to think of the next phase,
but you can't help it.
- Yes. - That's right.
That's why you make more memories with them.
I've been noticing that my cats have aged too.
That something's changed because they got old.
- You realized that. - Yes.
Yes. So it's somewhat sad,
but it's beautiful as well.
It's only natural.
(It's beautiful as well.)
(Exclaiming)
Eat well like you do now,
and let's go take photos again next year as well.
Okay?
(My Fairy, My Anju)
Well done.
(Next story)
(The first crisis that Moo Do Ra Ji faces)
(An endless steep slope)
(I almost went back home.)
(On top of that, they went off course.)
(The crew members were shaken.)
(That was a lurking problem for me.)
(I came too lightheartedly.)
(They'll have a dropout, which is unprecedented?)
(But...)
(The principle of Fun Run: We're one.)
(Not alone,)
(but together)
(They were serious about Moo Do Ra Ji.)
(They lifted each other up.)
(They revisited the meaning of friendship.)
We meant it.
(We're one team.)
(Together,)
(we don't give up.)
(Holding tightly)
(Let's Run No Matter What Happens)
(Breathing in)
(Gosh)
(Since he likes spicy food...)
(Bum June is in the middle of cooking something spicy.)
(YEONJUN came to see him!)
(YEONJUN came to help with the spring cleaning.)
(Putting it on)
(Bum June, trust me.)
(Let's quickly finish it and eat.)
(It's a piece of cake.)
- One, two, three. - Three.
Oh, dear.
It can't be lifted?
(Wait. Why wouldn't it budge?)
(Falling)
(I can only clean the floor after lifting the bed.)
(I'll hold it. You lift it.)
Do I remove it all?
(This is a brilliant idea!)
(Bright smile)
(What do you think?)
(It's good.)
(Two geniuses' spring cleaning)
(Hold on.)
(Falling)
(A difficult task even for the geniuses)
(Bumping)
(Screaming)
(We'll be able to finish it, won't we?)
Hold on.
(Completely drained)
(Dream Duo)